Donggeun: Just look at me?
Example of acrostic poem
Barber Razor Only look at me
Doni: Just look at me
Doni & Coni: Laser, Barbershop, Just look at me
Coni: There's no relation
Doni: Is there anyone in PRISTIN that can do it?
Donggeun: This seems difficult
The Amazing JR's acrostic poem ability
Doni: PRISTIN
Coni: Im Nayoung can
Coni's stubborn pick
Leader Lim's  Acrostic poem choice
Doni: Can Im Nayoung do it?
Coni: She can do it coolly
Doni: Im Nayoung can do it coolly
Doni: Then we will go with 'Raina'
Coni: Raina
Let me
Do well
Doni: Re
Nayoung: *speaking in gibberish*
Warm expression  with Silly  Alien Language
Doni: Excuse me?
My ears
Can't believe
Donggeun: Oh I know of that
Coni: Are you belittling us now?
First Encounter with New world's acrostic poem field
Self sense's bang explosion
Coni: *repeats gibberish*
Donggeun: She's just randomly speaking
Coni: It was like *gibberish*
Doni: I don't know what it is but we're done with 'Re'
More  Acrostic poems to look forward to
Coni: 'Re' pass
Coni: Ee-
Doni: Ee-
Nayoung: *more gibberish*
shame
less
Embarrassement  All over the place
Doni & Coni: *repeats gibberish*
Coni: *repeats gibberish*
Doni & Coni & Nayoung: Na-
Nayoung: Me, it's me *Produce 101 Nayana*
Andromeda's acrostic poem complete
Nayoung: Me, it's me
My
Misery
Doni: What did you say with 'Re'?
Nayoung: *repeats gibberish*
Only the feeling is the same
Surely A different alien from earlier
Roa: Oh it's the same
Doni: It feels different though
Caught
Raina: What's that?
Doni: I don't know
Nayoung: It's how Yang Sehyung sunbaenim does it
Indeed a plan
Steadily practice from Yang Sehyung st. acrostic poem
Coni & Raina: I see
Rena: Yang Sehyung
Coni: Yes
More shameless than ever
A mentality that doesn't  shake
Coni: I feel like another member will do well
lacking by 2%
Celebrities craving for jackpot
Doni: Who?
Coni: Dddiddi?
Doni: MC Ddiddi let's give it a try
MC Ddiddi's Acrostic poem choice
Xiyeon: Ah, yes
Coni: Ddiddi
Doni: Let's
Not Backing off
Xiyeon: Yes
Coni: With the CEO's name?
Doni: What's the name?
Raina: Han Sungsoo
Coni: Han Sungsoo CEO
the most difficult word
Han Sungsoo (Pledis CEO)
Doni: Han-
Xiyeon: Han Sungsoo
Oh my goodness
What is this
Doni: Han-
Xiyeon: Han Sungsoo
Heart made of steel
dropping formalities
This is definitely the dignity of PLEDIS' princess
Coni: That's the spirit
Coni: That's right
Only people who are hearing  are nervous
Doni: That was swaggy
Coni: That's right
Diddi holic uncles
Welcoming warmly the sweet acrostic poem
Coni: No formalities in 3 line acrostics
Doni: Of course
Coni: 'Sung' after Han Sungsoo
Doni & Kyulkyung: Sung-
Sung
Xiyeon: Sung
Xiyeon: I'm really hungry
I'm really hungry
Coni: I'm hungry
Doni: Han Seongsoo, I'm really hungry
Girl group  who did the Acrostic poem  late are doing well
Coni: Because you're on diet
Doni & Coni: Soo-
Xiyeon: Let's have a get-together on Wednesday
Let's go for dinner on Wednesday
Listen CEO
Doni & Coni: Soo-
Xiyeon: Let's have a get-together on Wednesday
Princess' dinner order
For the stomach
Sungyeon: Today
Acrostic poem's hidden big picture
Today's Wednesday
Doni: Get-together
Coni: CEO-nim you should at least do this much
Doni: This much is okay
Coni: MC Ddiddi worked so hard so
I Like
Pledis
Doni: Then
Coni: That was good
Doni: As for Baekho
Doni: Sword fighting for 7 years and Muay Thai, Baekho?!
Baekho: Yes
Did fencing for 7 years
Coni: You said you did sword fighting?
Baekho: Yes
Coni: Oh really?
Doni: Then
Great
Doni: Here's your sword
Then do
A fencing
demonstration please
Doni: Sword fighting
Martial Artist falling for Illegitimate martial arts
Coni: I'll throw you the watermelon
They keep ordering celebrities around
Baekho: Yes
Coni: 1, 2, 3
Coni: Ah I haven't thrown it yet
Baekho
Merong
Humiliation of 7 years of martial arts
Coni: Once again
Doni: Ah
Doni: Didn't you learn something like this?
Giving him a pen is asking for too much
Baekho: That seems quite difficult
Doni: But you said you learned it
Coni: Then let's
The one sitting next to Doni & Coni
Donggeun who is on more fire
Coni: I've thrown one
Per-
-fect
Coni: Look at that
Coni: I've thrown one
Donggeun Nice Shot
Coni: You did well
Coni: Turn around, the mandarin is behind you
Difficulty going from watermelon to a tangerine
It makes no sense but
Doni: He's good
Coni: Behind you
Donggeun doing a cut  Shyshyshy
Doni: He's good
Celebrity genius          Donggeun
I can't win
against that hyung...
Respect
Doni: He's samurai geun
Amount of responsibility cleared
Coni: Yes
Doni: Ren do you perhaps have a personal talent?
3rd level basement
Period of personal talents
Ren: As for me
Doni: Something you're good at
Ren: I don't really have a lot of personal talents but
Ren: Last time when I was on Produce 101, my gangster shoulders became a topic
The hero of
Produce 101's
Shoulder Gangster
Doni: How many cms?
Ren: They're really narrow now
The sudden wide shoulder magical talent
Ren: But if I put on my gangster shoulders they become really wide
Coni: Because you've exercised?
2 people who know nothing about PD101
Ren: No
Coni: Then?
Ren: I can make them wider right now
Doni & Coni: How do you do it?
Shoulder
Extension
The dongseangs first sight of the miracle talent
Yehana: Woah, that's really interesting
Ren: Should do it like this
Walking with a feeling is automatically loaded
Ren: I can lower my shoulders
Even if you see it you can't believe the mystery of the human body
Coni: They became much wider
Doni: How do you do it?
Xiyeon: It doesn't seem easy
Ren: Like this
Expansion of face instead of shoulder
This is incredible too
Xiyeon: I thought he was dislocating something
Ren: Firstly you have move your face to the back
Shoulder gangster STEP 1
Push your face back
Ren: To create an illusion, then
Not even
Step 1
Ren: You have to thrust this forward as much as you can
Shoulder gangster STEP 2
Move your shoulders forward
Coni: You extend so well
Ren: And you lift up your legs to create an illusion
Shoulder gangster STEP 3
Lift your legs
Doni: It's really fascinating
Just mango.jpg
Swollen mango.jpg
Raina: Looking at it in person is even more fascinating
Donggeun: So weird
Doni: It's like that dislocating neck magic
A scene from a manga in front of my eyes
?: For real
This is why he's someone who just came out of a manga
Coni: Now, you guys have to do something too right?
Doni: But Yuha's waist is really thin
Doni's eyes captured
the body talent
Yuha's ant waist
PRISTIN's
Doni: Let's measure Yuha's waist
3rd level basement's guinness book automatic challenge
size = record
Doni: As a personal talent
Doni: Who's our record holder?
Doni: AOA's Mina with 17.9"
17.9 inches AOA Mina
the still unbeatable record
Yuha: Really?
Doni: Like this
Golden ratio Yuha
PLEDIS representative
Record challenge
Rena: Unnie I will help you
Ant waist owner's arrival
Kyulkyung: PRISTIN's pride
Doni: I will measure it
Roa: The mic
Order as much as Olympic finals
Rena: We have to use inches
Doni: Using inches
Yuha: The waist
Roa: Lift your arms
Breathing
Difficulty
Doni: Please move the mic
Roa: Breathe in
Roa: Ah
Heartbeat
Kyulkyung: Unnie fighting!
Roa: You can do this
Roa: You can do it, hold it in
The many people who are
making the ant waist
Nayoung: You can do this
Doni: It's 12" right now
Still in breathing difficulty
Eunwoo: 12"?
Kyulkyung: It's probably 22"
Roa: Breathe in more
Doni: Wow amazing!
Doni: It's almost there
One eye looking forward to
the amazing record
Doni: What is this?
Roa: Perfectly straight, perfectly straight
Save
YuYu
Coni: Measure it straight
Doni: Oh it's up till here
Pulling in the reduced waist size
Doni: It's done
Doni: Wait a moment, sorry Yuha
Roa: Breathe in on the count of 1,2,3
This is like
Tug-of-War
Doni: It's 18" now, 18"
Creation of New Record
Weekly Idol
3rd level basement breaking new
Coni: A bit more
Yehana: 1, 2
Doni: Pull in now, right now
What is this?
Heated     Cheering
Coni: Alright
Doni: It's possible, it's possible
Doni: Wow, it's done
Holding her breath for the new record
Still not breathing
Coni: It's 18" now
Doni: So
Doni: Now Mina is 17.9"
Mysterious
Coni: Now 17"
Coni: 17"
There is a new record
Doni & Coni: 17"
Mina's record is currently 17 inches
Wow
Coni: 17"
Donggeun: Just have to wait a little more
Coni: Now
Touching mouth opening
Coni: 16.6"
16.6 inches!!!
Doni & Coni: 16.6"
Pristin's Yuha has the tiniest ant waist in girl groups
Breaking news
Doni: Amazing
Look at this honored face
Doni: 16.6"
Yuha: I couldn't breathe
Doni: Finally, Mina's waist record that was undefeated for two years
A record that took 2 years to break
Coni: Yes
Doni: It's 1.3" thinner than 17.7"
PRISTIN Yuha's 16.6 inches incredible record
Raina: Isn't this too forceful?
Can you do it like this?
a worried fairy
Doni: Mina did it like that too
Watching together
Minah's also forced record
episode 204, broadcast
Doni: She did it like that
Coni & Doni: How was it possible?
By the way
16.6 inches is an amazing size
Yuha: It was difficult
Coni: Were you born with it?
Doni: Originally?
This is all thanks to you guys who measured well
SsankYu
Yuha: I couldn't breathe so
Doni: Just because you hold your breath
16.6" which won't be beaten for a while
Doni: Doesn't necessarily mean it can be like that
Will wait for all idols to challenge
Coni: Can't be 16.6"
Doni: Nu'est is PLEDIS' first boy group
Doni: Pledis 1st male trainee was JR, oh is that so?
PLEDIS 1st male trainee JR
JR: Raina and I joined at the same time
How JR and Raina joined
even if we don't know the order
JR: Yeah we joined at the same time
Doni: You guys really joined the company at the same time?
Raina: JR, Lizzy & I joined at the same time
PLEDIS 2009's 3 new employees
Doni: Oh really?
JR: Nuna debuted
Then he was 15 years old
JR debuted 3 years after
JR: And became my sunbaenim
Raina: He was a total baby
Thanks to Raina's pretty treatment
6 years older
Raina: Jonghyun was always shy
Raina: "Hello nunas" like this
JR reenacting
Shy
Even now
Raina: He was a friend like that
Raina: I was like "Do you want some bread?"
Noona's eyes filled with precious (JR) Jonghyun's old days
Raina: "Thank you"
Raina: He was a friend like this really
Doni: She looked after you a lot
Raina: I gave him bread
JR: Yeah she looked after me a lot
JR: Because I was a male
JR: I lived with the manager alone
JR: As soon as I finished practice I ate ramyeon often
He used to eat ramen as the only male trainee
JR: That time, Nana & Raina bought me beef bone soup
Never forgetting noona's beef bone soup treat
Doni: Beef bone soup
Getting
Emotional
Coni: You would remember of course, beef bone soup from when you were a trainee
Coni: A simple but significant happiness
Touched
Warm
Raina: He was cute
Doni: So I heard you cooked jjajangramyeon alone for a year
Raina: Aigo
JR: That's right, twice a day
Doni: Twice a day
Doni: That's why today you will be cooking 18 servings
When Ramen talk starts,
it immediately starts boiling in 3rd level basement
ending the warmth
Raina: What?
Doni: Jjajangramyeon
Raina: Cooking it?
Coni: Yes
Doni: Here
Making 18 servings
of jjajang ramyeon
Mission right now
Doni: Jonghyun
Coni: But the Pledis kids cooked ramyeon last time
Remembering SEVENTEEN's ramen treat
Suddenly
Doni: Who was it then?
Coni: In Seventeen
Raina: Wasn't it Minggyu?
Coni: Minggyu
PLEDIS official chef Mingyu
Doni: His ramyeon
Coni: Was really well cooked
Doni: Was it 10 servings?
Coni: Minggyu cooks it really well
Doni: Minggyu looks like he owns a restaurant
The legendary cooking broadcast of 3rd level basement
Episode 308 broadcast
Doni: It's not easy to cook 15 servings
Housewife Ming's ramen cooking for 15 people
SEVENTEEN
Coni: Look at him getting the proportions right
Acknowledging PLEDIS handmade taste
Doni: None of the noodles overcooked
Minggyu: It's amazing right?
PLEDIS family's amazing taste
today too is aju nice?
Doni: Okay, Jonghyun
Doni: Will challenge cooking 18 servings of jjajangramyeon
Sunbae's difficulty UP
Ramen for 15          Jjajang ramyeon for 18 people
Raina & JR: Right now?
Today JR will cook jjajang ramyeon
JR: Alright
Coni: Please take care of us, Jonghyun
Slow
Relaxed
Doni: Start
JR: Yes
Doni: Now onto PRISTIN
Doni: PRISTIN
PRISTIN
Peutinie
Doni: Aegyo kings PRISTIN
Doni: In sync with Jo Youngpil's 'Bounce'
Doni: PRISTIN's trademark wink
Coni: Are you all doing it?
PRISITN: Yes
Peutin Girls'
Group Talent
Doni: What is this?
Doni: I'm really curious
You've got to have the flowers (be prepared) before you dismount
Doni: Are you rea-Oh they're already preparing
Ju Kyulkyung
(pretty enough to cause the fall of a country)
Doni: Okay, PRISTIN's bounce wink aegyo
Juicy
Ready
Doni: Singing the song too?
Jjajang Ready
Wink Ready
Same Space Different Feel
Eunwoo: Yes
Doni: With the song?
Rena: No, it's with the song
Doni: Ok
To HIghs
Get your Video&GIF tools Ready
Doni: Music please
Hello, we are Pristin and...
Starting now, we're going to capture your heart
Bang
Ya
Coni: You can't be shy
TV watching HIgh's hearts are bounce bounce
Coni: You're the ones who volunteered
Suddenly re-emerging cluelessly upright boy
Aron: Xiyeon is not winking though
Doni: Wait a moment
Counterfeit
Wink
Doni: This is
Doni: Who did you say couldn't do it?
Baekho: Xiyeon
Saw in the midst of all
Misters with such great vision
Coni: Xiyeon?
Doni: Try doing it, music please
Having brief wink verification
Coni: Ddiddi
Doni: Start
Coni: It's not working
Doni: Wink
Seems like severe magnesium deficiency
Coni: You don't know what a wink is?
Doni & Coni: Just on one side
?: Her eyelids
Baekho: It's like something's stuck in her eye
Annoying teasing just like a real older brother
Doni: Just one side, try the left side
Cannot freely control with my will
A bodily mystery
Doni: Just the left side
Doni: Stop moving your right side
Coni: Did you get sand in your eye?
Another realistic older brother
Regardless of what's happening NO interest
Coni: Just one side
Doni: It doesn't work
Coni: Is there anyone who can do it well?
Nayoung: No, I can't
Wink police randomly begins spot checks
Coni: Excuse me? Can't you be more positive?
Coni, Stone, want to give it a try?
Prepared variety attitude
Pristin who doesn't know NO
Nayoung: I will give it a try
Doni: Music please, start
Top focus
Doesn't look even once
Kyulkyung: The mouth must be covered
Protects unnie's beauty
Must cover my unnie's mouth
Starts off well
Roa: You must match it well
AGH
Doni: Why? Are you hurting somewhere?
Coni: Your eyes are cramping
Doni: Eyes can cramp too?
This side  is only walking the noodle path
Helper Ren added
World of their own
Coni: Because she strained them all of a sudden
Doni: Eyes can cramp?
Perhaps world's first
Idol suffers wink-induced  cramping
Nayoung: I can't open my eyes
Coni: Who's good at this?
Out of Pristin
who is the
wink expert?
Roa & Kyulkyung: Me
Coni: Roa
Doni & Coni: Roa & Kyulkyung, you two
Roa: Let's do it quickly
Recover glory
The time has come to show-off worthy winks
Doni: Music, Ddiddi please take a good look
Xiyeon: Yes
Doni: Music please
KyulkyungXRoa
The real
Bounce Wink
Sungyeon: They're really good
Error
Output
Coni: Roa's a machine
Doni: Wait a moment, Kyulkyung is bad at it too
Doni: You try it alone, do it alone
Was a group talent but
One by one eliminated
Doni: Start
Sungyeon: Her mouth
Doni: Don't move your mouth
Continuously occuring  eyes X mouth synced movement
Doni: Close your mouth
Kyulkyung
crashes
Xiyeon: Close your lips
Doni: Wait a moment
Doni: It's not working out
Causes people to give up winking, the devil's personal talent
Doni: Only Roa can do it
Roa: I apologize
Doni: Then who wrote this
Yuha: Yuyu
Doni: It's not working out
Doni: Yuha it's not working out
Fast
Apology
Yuha: I'm sorry
Doni: This doesn't work, only works for Roa
Is this
difficult?
Doni: Raina
Doni: How do feel looking at the rookies do aegyo?
Actually this area's leading expert
Doni: Raina used to do it a lot back then
Raina: I did it a lot
Raina: Reminds me of my older days
Raina: I was good at it too
Doni: So Raina...
Raina: What? Where?
Aegyo legend Orange Caramel's Raina
Raina: I do it while matching with this song?
Ducked head
When given noodles, forgot about filming
Doni: Once on this side and that
Doni: This
Doni: You can't do it like a comedian
Due to old age, cut off entertainment
Doni: You can't do it like this
Raina: I will do it well normally
Normally
Raina's wink bounce
Eunwoo: Fighting
Doni: Music please
More than anyone, rhythmical wink bounce
Coni: She's still got it
Firsthand spectating
Orange Caramel's
godly aegyo
Doni: Of course, Raina
Like this, the juniors
once again learn a lesson
Doni: You were the best
Me too
Coni: She's still got it
Doni: You were the best
Raina: I should use this as my personal talent
Doni: This is Raina's
Right away profile edited
Doni: Raina
Coni: Raina who can do the bounce wink
Unintentionally Raina gains a personal talent
Coni: Yes
Doni: Next, expressionless leader Stone Nayoung's 'Sweetheart' aegyo
Nayoung: Expressionless ver. is scary so I will mix it with the original ver.
Blank faceXaegyo
mixed, brand new
'Oppaya''
Doni: Can't we have a look at the Expressionless ver. first ?
Doni: But I don't know why she is Stone Nayoung
Doesn't know Pristin, doesn't get Stone Nayoung
Coni: Stiff like a stone
Expressionless Girl Crush Stone Nayoung
Coni: It's your cute nickname right? 'Stone Nayoung'
Doni: Let's have a look
Stone Crush
Nayoung
Oppa-ya
Doni: Show us please
As soon as it starts, NG
Doni: I don't think this will work
Oppa-ya
Wanna fight?
Doni: I don't think this will work
Nayoung: I will mix it
Doni: It's too scary
Aegyo causes heart to race for a different reason
Nayoung: I will combine them
At this time
Still has head ducked
Doni: Kinda feels like watching "The Mimic" (a horror movie)
This much?
Full effort
18 packets of seasoning squeezed, arm surely hurts
Coni: I was super surprised
Doni: Let's combine them and do it
Nayoung: Yes
Expressionless X Aegyo mix
Nayoung 'Oppaya'
Replay
Doni: Start
World's cutest stone
Brutal
Frozen
Cute
Happy
Warm stone
Cold stone
Coni: She changes back and forth
Doni: How did she do that?
Sudden changes
Fully into full-package Nayoung's charms
Coni: She changes back and forth
He-het
Coni: Showing your expression
Doni: I don't think I can date you
Doni: Which of the two are you more comfortable with?
First time seeing
analyzes character
Doni: Which is closer to your actual personality?
Nayoung: I'm uncomfortable with both
Aegyo or stern both aren't her type
Doni: Then what image do you have?
Stone Nayoung, the more you know, a mysterious woman
Rena: She has a lot of aegyo in daily life
Don't mistake
Nayoung's true form is daily-life aegyo leader
Roa: She has a lot of aegyo but
Roa: It's probably because she blanks out
Doni: That could be it
Actually honey Nayoung
Doni: Eunwoo
Eunwoo: Yes?
Pristin's Aegyo final boss Eunwoo
Doni: I heard that you're the final boss of aegyo
Eunwoo: Yes, that's right
Right away
admits
Coni: Yes, that's right
Doni: It's true?
Kyulkyung: Kind of aegyo that calls for a fist
Here and there fists start to come out
Doni: Aegyo that calls for the fist
Eunwoo: Yes
Fist Calling Aegyo possessor
Doni: What kind of aegyo do you do to your members usually?
Usual aegyo towards the members?
Eunwoo: For example, towards Nayoung unnie
Eunwoo: Nanangie
Nayoung unnie
Nanangie~
Except Eunwoo, this is not a still JPG file
Eunwoo: Nanangie
Very cold atmosphere
Coni: The fist is here
Even at the start
Amazing ability to make someone frustrated
Coni: The fist does rise
Doni: Then what does Nayoung do?
Nayoung's highly anticipated response
Coni: Nayoung can just give her a punch
Nayoung: No, we do it together
Like a daily-aegyo leader replies with aegyo
Doni: Oh together? Please show us once
Eunwoo: Nanangie
Nayoung: Nurangie
Eunwoo: Nunu is hungry
Suddenly blows
Doni: The members are leaving
Coni: Right now Sungyeon is
Doni: Are you alright?
Raina: She turned her head
No shield
Calls out what's wrong, blunt sisters
Coni: Xiyeon was getting up to leave
Doni: Eunwoo, let's go
Until now,
just merely
a prologue
Eunwoo: Oppaya?
Doni: Music please
Pristin's aegyo queen
Nunu's 'Oppaya'
will be revealed in 60 seconds
Doni: Music please
Nurangdoongie
Eunwoo
Oppa-ya
Without an ounce of shame, model aegyo
Because it's not business, even more struggling colleagues
Shivers
Scared
Giiggles, how fun
Lacking nothing, perfect standard aegyo
Even calls for one's own fist
Nunu's cute fist-calling aegyo
Doni: Nu'est are you ready?
You thought you'd get by for free?
Nu-dong, are you ready?
Crown of head catches the eye
Ren: Aegyo?
Doni: Aegyo
Ren: With that song?
Doni: 'Sweetheart'
Coni: Jonghyun?
JR: Yes?
Today's sacrificial lamb has been selected
Coni: Jonghyun?
JR: Yes?
Emerges
Fresh, innocent, youthful
Ren: Show us your aegyo
Right when it's time to bring
noodle-obsessed JR back on screen
Coni: You're too concerned about the jajjangmyeon
Ren: This is
Coni: In this circumstance
JR: Oh am I doing it?
Coni: Of course
Coni: Don't pretend that you don't know, you saw it all
Don't act clueless
Well I did see
JR: I've seen it
Doni: Music please
Lovely turtle
JR
Oppa-ya
Doni: Music please
Boogie
Explosive aegyo, where is my dignity?
My colleague's business
How pitiful...
Even brings out hide-and-seek
Even more surprising
Hides behind the ramen
Ha-hat
Acknowledged
Doni: Then
Coni: Baekho?
After filming, back to business
Coni: Donggeunie?
Doni: Tough aegyo
Surpassing bandit sexy, private aegyo time
Doni: Yes
Aegyo to open LOVE's hearts
Doni: Our Dongho
Doni: Music cue
Next Wednesday 6 PM
able to watch
Weekly Idol
Doni: Pledis Family arcade
Endless energy rich Pledis family
Donggeun: Can't you speak properly?
Family feud begins?
Ren: Just look at me
Your voice
can't be heard!
Ren: Just look at me
Baekho: Am I the only fool?
Can't hide Baekho's clueless charms
Baekho: Fool?
Power X Pretty
Brand new
Athlete-dol birthed
Pristin: Yehana!
Pristin: One, two, one, two
1, 2 1, 2
Speed in their hearts is 100km
Aron: Why are they doing it like that?
Lower body workout
Extreme game experience
Pledis family's
random play dance
grand challenge
Pretty girl next to a pretty girl next to pretty Ren
Basement 3rd floor
Dance accuracy 105%
? *Me too* (lyrics)
Extreme family game night
the result of this competition is?
Xiyeon: Weekly
All: Idol
Next Wednesday 6 PM
the only time to watch live
*Catellenna* *We Like*
PRISTIN - WE LIKE